Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 11 and District 11 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 11 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1147
    - Local 1147 Incoming Correspondence, 1945-1948 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - David Scribner to Matson Regarding Taft Hartley and Negotiations, September 8, 1947; 5.
    - Local 1147 Outgoing Correspondence, 1939-1948 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - William Forseth to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, December 2, 1943; 1.
      - Paul Heidman to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Constitution, January 13, 1943; 2.
      - Charles Matson to H.W. Clark Regarding Negotiations, January 3, 1946; 3.
      - Matson Regarding Negotiations, January 3, 1946; 4.
      - Matson to UE Regarding Negotiations, January 29, 1946; 5.
      - Matson to UE Regarding Negotiations, January 14, 1947; 6.
      - Matson to UE Regarding Negotiations and Taft Hartley, September 5, 1947; 7.
      - Matson to UE Regarding Negotiations, January 9, 1948; 8.
      - Carl Schuhe to James Matles Regarding Organization and Wages, December 1939; 9.
      - Schuhe to UE Regarding Officers, January 8, 1940; 10.
      - Schuhe to Matles Regarding Contracts, Negotiations, and Wages, November 3, 1941; 11.
      - Schuhe to Emspak Regarding Contracts and Officers, February 1942; 12.
      - John Tarnowski to General Executive Board Regarding Dues and Veterans, June 30, 1945; 13.
      - Tarnowski to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, January 3, 1946; 14.
    - Local 1147 Negotiations, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Julius Emspak to Louis Majors, January 17, 1947; 1.
      - Majors to Emspak, January 22, 1947; 2.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, January 28, 1947; 3.
      - Majors to Emspak, January 29, 1947; 4.
    - Local 1147 Disbanding, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Julius Emspak to Anthony DeMaio, November 15, 1954; 1.
      - DeMaio to Emspak, November 18, 1954; 2.
    - Local 1147 Charter Application, October 24, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Local 1148
    - Local 1148 Officers Lists, February 26, 1944-February 1947 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Local 1148 Membership Resolution Regarding Disbanding, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Local 1148 Incoming Correspondence, 1940-1943 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Robert Kirkwood to John Bobes Regarding UE News and Midwest Labor, November 2, 1943; 1.
      - James Matles to Stanley Nelson Regarding Contracts, October 10, 1940; 2.
    - Local 1148 Outgoing Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - H.J. Hoss to UE Regarding Unemployment, March 1942; 1.
      - John Kubes to UE Regarding UE News and Midwest Labor, October 16, 1943; 2.
    - Local 1148 Organization and Contract, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Charter Application, July 23, 1940; 1.
      - Leonard Lageman to James Matles, October 7, 1940; 2.
      - Matles to Lageman, October 10, 1940; 3.
    - Local 1148 Military Contracts, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Julius Emspak to Buford Eastman, April 3, 1942; 1.
      - William Mauseth to Emspak, April 6, 1942; 2.
    - Local 1148 Correspondence, Winston Johns to UE Regarding Disbanding, November 28, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Local 1149
    - Local 1149 Officers Lists, April 1943-April 6, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Local 1149 Incoming Correspondence, 1940-1948 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - P. Billings to Local 1149 Regarding Contracts and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, December 11, 1940; 1.
      - Neil Brant to William Holloway Regarding War Labor Board and Productivity, December 10, 1942; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Art Hill Regarding Boycotts, December 11, 1940; 3.
      - Emspak to Ted Kant Regarding Per Capita, October 10, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Albert Hannum Regarding Finances, December 15, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to Bessie Pauls Regarding Dues and Veterans, June 27, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Harold Dolson Regarding Strikes, August 26, 1948; 7.
      - Emspak to Viola Davis Regarding Strikes, September 13, 1948; 8.
      - James Matles to Ted Kent Regarding Staff Members, May 13, 1941; 9.
      - Matles to Joe Cetner Regarding Staff Members, May 13, 1941; 10.
      - Matles to Cetner Regarding Radio Industry, October 7, 1941; 11.
      - Secretary of David Scribner to Cetner Regarding Veterans and Seniority, February 18, 1946; 12.
      - Unsigned Letter to F. DuPont, November 23, 1942; 13.
    - Local 1149 Outgoing Correspondence, 1941-1948 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Joseph Cetner to UE Regarding Officers, March 14, 1941; 1.
      - Cetner to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 2, 1941; 2.
      - Cetner to David Scribner Regarding Veterans and Seniority, February 12, 1946; 3.
      - Harold Dalson to Lewis Schwellenbach Regarding Negotiations, May 5, 1947; 4.
      - Viola Davis to UE Regarding Officers, January 1945; 5.
      - Davis to Julius Emspak Regarding Strikes, October 1, 1948; 6.
      - Frank DuPont to Harold Matles Regarding Overtime, November 23, 1942; 7.
      - DuPont to Emspak Regarding Overtime, November 24, 1942; 8.
      - DuPont to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Officers, February 23, 1943; 9.
      - Arthur Hill to Emspak Regarding UE News and AFL Inter-union Rivalry, August 7, 1941; 10.
      - Hill to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 26, 1941; 11.
      - William Holloway to Matles Regarding War Labor Board, December 10, 1942; 12.
      - Holloway to Emspak Regarding Political Action and Taxation, May 11, 1943; 13.
      - Holloway to Emspak Regarding Officers, March 24, 1944; 14.
      - Ted Kent to Emspak Regarding Constitutions, February 20, 1941; 15.
      - Kent to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Organization, May 2, 1941; 16.
      - Robert Kirkwood to Russell Nixon Regarding Sub-contracting and War Production, April 30, 1942; 17.
      - Bessie Pauls to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, June 18, 1945; 18.
    - Local 1149 Leaflets, 1941, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - "Attention" Regarding Organization, August 1941; 1.
      - "Need A Radio" Regarding Strikes and Boycotts, September 7, 1948; 2.
    - Local 1149 Strike and Inter-union Rivalry, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Memo, December 9, 1948; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest DeMaio, January 25, 1949; 2.
    - Local 1149 Miscellaneous, 1940-1946 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Charter Application, October 24, 1940; 1.
      - James Matles to Neil Brant Regarding Staff Member, December 31, 1942; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Per Capita, November 7, 1944; 3.
      - Labor Department Reemployment Provisions, May 8, 1945; 4.
      - Alice Smith to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 28, 1946; 5.
  - Local 1150
    - Local 1150 Constitution, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Local 1150 Contract, August 31, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Local 1150 Officers Lists, December 14, 1943-January 27, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Local 1150 Irving Krane Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1949 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Julius Emspak to Irving Krane Regarding Finances, July 28, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Chicago Transformer Organization, October 8, 1943; 2.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Krane Regarding Dues, July 18, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Dues and Veterans, July 27, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Dues and Veterans, October 16, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Hurley Machine, February 1, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Solar Manufacturing White Collar Workers, April 17, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Finances, October 18, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Finances, November 10, 1945; 9.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Jensen Radio Strike and William Welsh, July 8, 1947; 10.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Cory Corporation Strike, November 20, 1947; 11.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Goodman Manufacturing Strike, June 7, 1948; 12.
      - Emspak to Krane Regarding Cory Strike, March 24, 1949; 13.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Krane Regarding African-Americans, July 28, 1944; 14.
      - Fitzgerald to Krane Regarding Lanovel Stewards, December 2, 1946; 15.
      - Fitzgerald to Krane Regarding Wages, June 6, 1947; 16.
      - James Matles to Krane Regarding Remmington Rand Organization, December 18, 1945; 17.
      - Herbert Morais to Krane Regarding Chicago Essex Wire Contract and Wages, June 4, 1946; 18.
      - David Ratner to Krane Regarding Finances, May 27, 1949; 19.
      - David Roths to Krane Regarding Cory Strike, January 11, 1949; 20.
      - Frances Sayler to Krane Regarding Taft Hartley Affidavits, November 14, 1949; 21.
      - David Scribner to Krane Regarding UE Constitution, July 11, 1946; 22.
      - Scribner to Krane Regarding Grievance Procedure and War Labor Board with Case Rulings, September 30, 1943; 23.
      - Scribner to Krane Regarding General Transformer, WLB, and National Labor Relations Board, October 9, 1943; 24.
    - Local 1150 Irving Krane Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1949 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Irving Krane to David Scribner Regarding Hurley Machine Organization, May 11, 1943; 1.
      - Krane to Neil Brant Regarding Hurley Machine Organization, May 20, 1943; 2.
      - Krane to Brant Regarding Hurley Machine Organization and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry with Letter to James Matles, May 20, 1943; 3.
      - Krane to Matles Regarding Hurley Machine Organization and IAM Inter-union Rivalry, July 20, 1943; 4.
      - Krane to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, July 30, 1943; 5.
      - Krane to Matles Regarding Cinch Manufacturing, War Labor Board, and Union Shop, September 27, 1943; 6.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Chicago Transformer Negotiations, October 6, 1943; 7.
      - Krane to UE Regarding Dues, July 14, 1944; 8.
      - Krane to Ray Klausner Regarding Dues and Veterans, July 24, 1944; 9.
      - Krane to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding African-Americans and Women, July 25, 1944; 10.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Goodman and Clayton Mark Organization, Hurley Machine Inter-union Rivalry, and WLB Negotiations, July 31, 1944; 11.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Goodman Manufacturing Organization, October 20, 1944; 12.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Goodman Manufacturing Organization and Factionalism, October 27, 1944; 13.
      - Krane to Ruth Roemer Regarding Hurley Machine Negotiations, Company Union, NLRB, and WLB, January 16, 1945; 14.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, Hurley Machine, WLB, and NLRB, January 16, 1945; 15.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 17, 1945; 16.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Solar Manufacturing White Collar Workers and Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists, and Technicians Inter-union Rivalry, April 2, 1945; 17.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, April 18, 1945; 18.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Hurley Machine Negotiations and NLRB Firings, June 27, 1945; 19.
      - Krane to Matles Regarding Officers, October 23, 1945; 20.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 23, 1945; 21.
      - Krane to Matles Regarding Hurley Manufacturing and Moulders Inter-union Rivalry, December 28, 1945; 22.
      - Krane to Matles Regarding GE and Westinghouse Strikes, January 26, 1946; 23.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Exide Strike, March 29, 1946; 24.
      - Krane to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Contract, May 11, 1946; 25.
      - Krane to Scribner Regarding UE Constitution, June 28, 1946; 26.
      - Krane to Fitzgerald Regarding Stewards Banquet, November 21, 1946; 27.
      - Krane to Matles Regarding Salary and Westinghouse, January 20, 1947; 28.
      - Krane to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Wages, June 2, 1947; 29.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Jensen Radio and Wm. Welsh Strikes, July 2, 1947; 30.
      - Krane to Philip Murray Regarding Illinois Congress of Industrial Organizations, September 17, 1947; 31.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Goodman Manufacturing Strike, May 21, 1948; 32.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Sunbeam Membership Drive, July 22, 1948; 33.
      - Krane to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Cory Strike, January 11, 1949; 34.
      - Krane to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, January 14, 1949; 35.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Cory Strike, March 14, 1949; 36.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Cory Strike, March 30, 1949; 37.
      - Krane to David Ratner Regarding Finances, May 25, 1949; 38.
      - Krane to Emspak Regarding Finances and Per Capita, October 13, 1949; 39.
      - Krane to Matles Regarding Factionalism, Sunbeam, and Inter-union Rivalry, December 14, 1949; 40.
    - Local 1150 Robert Kirkwood Incoming Correspondence, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Julius Emspak to Robert Kirkwood Regarding Legislation, September 25, 1942; 1.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Kirkwood Regarding Conscription, February 5, 1942; 2.
      - Fitzgerald to Kirkwood Regarding Staff Members with Birth Announcement, September 24, 1942; 3.
      - James Matles to Kirkwood Regarding Organization, 4.
      - Matles to Kirkwood Regarding GE X-ray and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, June 29, 1942; 5.
      - Matles to Kirkwood Regarding Chicago Transformer Organization, July 28, 1942; 6.
      - Matles to Kirkwood Regarding Chicago Transformer Negotiations and War Labor Board, September 29, 1942; 7.
      - Matles to Kirkwood Regarding Conscription, October 13, 1942; 8.
    - Local 1150 Robert Kirkwood Outgoing Correspondence, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Robert Kirkwood to James Matles Regarding Local 1111 War Labor Board Negotiations, February 18, 1942; 1.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Illinois Manufacturing Association, March 12, 1942; 2.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Local 1111 Negotiations, March 30, 1942; 3.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Organization and Unemployment with Memo, March 30, 1942; 4.
      - Kirkwood to Russ Nixon Regarding General Transformer, War Contracts, and Unemployment, April 14, 1942; 5.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Radio Conference, April 17, 1942; 6.
      - Kirkwood to Nixon Regarding Sub-contracting, April 17, 1942; 7.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Pioneer Negotiation, April 29, 1942; 8.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Pioneer Negotiation and WLB, May 11, 1942; 9.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Pioneer Negotiation and WLB, May 21, 1942; 10.
      - Kirkwood to L.P. Hyland Regarding Pioneer Negotiation and WLB, May 23, 1942; 11.
      - Kirkwood to Frances Perkins Regarding Pioneer Negotiation and WLB, May 23, 1942; 12.
      - Kirkwood to Donald Nelson Regarding Pioneer Negotiation and WLB, May 23, 1942; 13.
      - Kirkwood to John Steelman Regarding Pioneer Negotiation and WLB, May 23, 1942; 14.
      - Kirkwood to William Davis Regarding Pioneer Negotiation and WLB, May 23, 1942; 15.
      - Kirkwood to Steelman Regarding Pioneer Negotiation, May 28, 1942; 16.
      - Kirkwood to Neil Brant Regarding Pioneer Negotiation, May 30, 1942; 17.
      - Kirkwood to Brant Regarding Pioneer Negotiation and WLB, June 3, 1942; 18.
      - Kirkwood to T. Hyland Regarding Pioneer Negotiation and WLB, June 3, 1942; 19.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Chicago Transformer Organization, July 29, 1942; 20.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 12, 1942; 21.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 14, 1942; 22.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Chicago Transformer Organization, Company Union, and Women, August 17, 1942; 23.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 17, 1942; 24.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Local 1153 Strike, August 17, 1942; 25.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Chicago Transformer Organization and Staff Finances, August 29, 1942; 26.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Western Electric Kolmar Organization and Company Union, September 19, 1942; 27.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 19, 1942; 28.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Chicago Transformer Negotiation, September 25, 1942; 29.
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Universal Battery, October 12, 1942; 30.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Arrests, Organization, and Stewart Warner, November 10, 1942; 31.
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Elcor Negotiation, International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, Strikes, and WLB, December 12, 1942; 32.
    - Local 1150 General Incoming Correspondence, 1942-1956 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Janet Barish to Byron Edwards Regarding Staff Members, March 24, 1955; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Ina Lu Miaux Regarding Dues, February 3, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Alfreda Ciba Regarding Local Shops, April 27, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Pat Amato Regarding Finances, May 17, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Amato Regarding Finances, June 30, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Lee Lundgren Regarding PAC, August 7, 1947; 6.
      - Emspak to Amato Regarding Cory and Dues, August 26, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak to Lundgren Regarding PAC, October 31, 1947; 8.
      - Emspak to Lundgren Regarding Cory Strike, December 5, 1947; 9.
      - Emspak to Julia Godinas Regarding Cory Strike, July 13, 1948; 10.
      - Emspak to Godinas Regarding Goodruck Manufacturing Strike, July 13, 1948; 11.
      - Emspak to Fred Dutner Regarding Cory Strike, November 3, 1950; 12.
      - Emspak to Dutner Regarding Vacations, January 14, 1952; 13.
      - Emspak to Ernest Judth Regarding National Strike Fund, October 23, 1952; 14.
      - Emspak to Judth Regarding General Motors Labs Strike, July 30, 1953; 15.
      - Emspak to Judth Regarding Factionalism and Staff Finances, March 9, 1955; 16.
      - Emspak to Judth Regarding Mailing List and Factionalism, June 10, 1955; 17.
      - Emspak to Judth Regarding Mailing List and Factionalism, June 22, 1955; 18.
      - Emspak to Thomas Byrne Regarding Strikes, February 29, 1956; 19.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Judth Regarding Finances, October 30, 1953; 20.
      - James Matles to Amato Regarding Staff Members, January 28, 1942; 21.
      - Matles to Amato Regarding Cinch Organization, May 24, 1943; 22.
      - Matles to Loudgren Regarding Exide Negotiation and Factionalism, March 20, 1948; 23.
      - Matles to Amato Regarding Staff Members, June 14, 1948; 24.
      - Matles to Lundgren Regarding Exide Negotiation, October 8, 1948; 25.
      - Matles to Amato Regarding Mailing Lists, March 29, 1949; 26.
      - Matles to Lundgren Regarding Wages and Exide, August 5, 1949; 27.
      - Matles to Irving Krane Regarding Factionalism, December 15, 1949; 28.
      - Matles to Dutner Regarding Staff Members, Exide Negotiation, and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 19, 1951; 29.
      - Matles to Dutner Regarding Staff Members, January 29, 1951; 30.
      - Matles to Dutner Regarding Exide and Finances, July 6, 1951; 31.
      - Matles to Dutner Regarding Exide and Inter-union Rivalry, July 19, 1951; 32.
      - Matles to Dutner Regarding Staff Finances, August 28, 1952; 33.
      - Matles to Dutner Regarding Staff Members, Bould Battery, and United Mine Workers Inter-union Rivalry with January 27, 1953, Memo, January 26, 1953; 34.
      - Matles to Dutner Regarding Cinch Manufacturing and Inter-union Rivalry, May 8, 1953; 35.
      - Matles to Dutner Regarding Publicity, December 21, 1953; 36.
      - Matles to Dutner Regarding Cinch Manufacturing and Inter-union Rivalry, May 20, 1954; 37.
      - Matles to Judth Regarding Per Capita, June 17, 1955; 38.
      - Matles to Judth Regarding Welsh Strike, July 8, 1955; 39.
      - Matles to Judth Regarding Welsh Strike, August 4, 1955; 40.
      - David Ratner to Amato Regarding NLRB, January 18, 1950; 41.
      - Ratner to Amato Regarding Finances, March 1, 1951; 42.
      - Secretary of Joseph Turkowski to Dutner Regarding Staff Finances, August 29, 1952; 43.
    - Local 1150 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1942-1955 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Pat Amato to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 23, 1942; 1.
      - Amato to Matles Regarding Finances and Organization, April 27, 1943; 2.
      - Amato to Matles Regarding Finances and Organization, May 11, 1943; 3.
      - Amato to Matles Regarding Cinch Manufacturing Organization and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, May 14, 1943; 4.
      - Amato to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, May 19, 1943; 5.
      - Amato to Emspak Regarding Officers, July 23, 1943; 6.
      - Amato to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Membership, November 6, 1943; 7.
      - Amato to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, June 13, 1944; 8.
      - Amato to Matles Regarding Staff Members, Chicago Transformer, and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, May 12, 1948; 9.
      - Amato to Fitzgerald Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, December 7, 1948; 10.
      - Amato to David Ratner Regarding Finances, January 17, 1950; 11.
      - Amato to UE News Regarding Benjamin and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, November 17, 1950; 12.
      - Fred Dutner to Emspak Regarding Cory Strike, October 27, 1950; 13.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding Exide Contract, IUE Inter-union Rivalry, and Staff Members, December 29, 1950; 14.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding Exide, IUE Inter-union Rivalry, and Staff Members, January 22, 1951; 15.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 2, 1951; 16.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, Exide, and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 15, 1951; 17.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding Exide and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 29, 1951; 18.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 21, 1952; 19.
      - Dutner to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, August 15, 1952; 20.
      - Dutner to Joseph Turkowski Regarding Staff Finances, August 28, 1952; 21.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding Cinch Manufacturing, IUE and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, and Goodman Negotiations, May 4, 1953; 22.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding General Motors Labs Strike, July 3, 1953; 23.
      - Dutner to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 27, 1953; 24.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding Goodman Negotiations, Cinch Manufacturing, and Inter-union Rivalry with International Association of Machinists, UAW, and IUE, April 30, 1954; 25.
      - Dutner to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Members, June 18, 1954; 26.
      - Dutner to Matles Regarding Brand Sheet Metal and Inter-union Rivalry with IAM, IBEW, and UAW, June 21, 1954; 27.
      - Byron Edwards to Matles Regarding United Motors Service Negotiations, February 27, 1953; 28.
      - Edwards to Matles Regarding Jensen Manufacturing and IBEW and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 16, 1955; 29.
      - Edwards to Matles Regarding Jensen Manufacturing, IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, and Goodman and Welsh Strike, June 3, 1955; 30.
      - Ernest Judth to Matles Regarding GM Labs Strike, July 13, 1953; 31.
      - Judth to Fitzgerald Regarding Strikes, IUE Inter-union Rivalry, and Per Capita, October 19, 1953; 32.
      - Judth to Fitzgerald Regarding Per Capita, October 17, 1953; 33.
      - Judth to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Staff Finances, March 8, 1945; 34.
      - Judth to Fitzgerald Regarding Mailing List, June 8, 1955; 35.
      - Ina La Miaux to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Elcor, January 5, 1943; 36.
      - La Miaux to Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board, March 9, 1943; 37.
      - Ragnar Lofgren to Matles Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry and Sunbeam, December 14, 1949; 38.
      - Wilhelmina Long to Barish Regarding Staff Members, December 2, 1953; 39.
      - Leland Mathis to Emspak Regarding Shop Newspapers, May 26, 1947; 40.
      - William Mullins to Matles Regarding Welsh Strike and African-Americans, June 22, 1950; 41.
      - Raymond Shellenberger to Matles Regarding Flagraising Ceremony and Elcor, November 10, 1942; 42.